<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>ZHANG Shuo</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/</link>
        <description>Recent content on ZHANG Shuo</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dong020524.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/contact/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/contact/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;email&lt;/strong&gt;                  szhang@lsec.cc.ac.cn.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;website&lt;/strong&gt;        http://lsec.cc.an.cn/~szhang/.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;tel&lt;/strong&gt;                            +86-10-82541578&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Education</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/education/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/education/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Aug 2008 - Aug 2009, &lt;strong&gt;Postdoctoral Research Associate&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Department of Mathematics&lt;/em&gt;, Pennsylvania State University, USA.        Mentor: Professor Jinchao Xu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sep 2003 - Jun 2008, &lt;strong&gt;Graduate student&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;School of Mathematical Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, Peking University, China.      Doctor supervisors: Professors Ming Wang and Zhiping Li.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sep 1999 - Jun 2003, &lt;strong&gt;Undergraduate student&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;School of Mathematical Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, Shandong University, China.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Professional Experience</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/profrssional/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/profrssional/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Jan 2020 -                               &lt;strong&gt;Schoolteacher&lt;/strong&gt;, University of Chinese Academy of Sciences, China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 2018 -                              &lt;strong&gt;Certified teacher for universities&lt;/strong&gt;, Certification no.: 20181100171005778.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 2013 - Aug 2014       &lt;strong&gt;Visiting scholar&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Department of Mathematics&lt;/em&gt;, The pennsylvania State University, USA.      Host: Professor Jinchao Xu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 2009 -                               &lt;strong&gt;Assistant professor, Associate professor&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Academy of Mathematics and System Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, Chinese Academy of Sciences, China.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Funds and Projects</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/funds/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/funds/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;PI    &lt;strong&gt;NSFC Program&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Low-degree optimal finite element methods of non-Ciarlet type on unstructured grids&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (NSFC 12271512, 2023-2026).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PI    &lt;strong&gt;NSFC Program&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Asymptotically structure-preserving order-reduced computational methods for fourth-order elliptic partial differential equations and related problems&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (NSFC 11871465, 2019-2022).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PI    &lt;strong&gt;NSFC Program&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Finite element methods for elastic strain gradient problems&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (NSFC 11471026, 2015-2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PI    &lt;strong&gt;NSFC Program&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Optimal solvers for finite element system of fourth order problems&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (NSFC 11101415, 2012-2014).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PI    &lt;strong&gt;Scientific Research Foundation for the Returned Overseas Chinese Scholars, State Education Ministry Program&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Effective fast finite element methods for fourth order partial differential equation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (Grant NO. Y390041G23).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ptcp    &lt;strong&gt;Strategic Priority Research Program of Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Formation, Evolution and Habitability of Terrestrial Planets&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, (XDB 41000000, 2020-2024).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Activities organised</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/activity/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/activity/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Aug 28-29, 2023 &lt;strong&gt;Progress in Finite Element and Galerkin-type Methods&lt;/strong&gt;, MS in the Jing-Jin-Ji plus Conference on Computational Mathematics, Taiyuan, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 16-18, 2023 &lt;strong&gt;Eigenvalue problems: numerical methods and pplications&lt;/strong&gt;, MS in the Annual Conference on Computational Mathematics 2023, Nanjing, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oct 8-11, 2021 &lt;strong&gt;Eigenvalue problems in photonic and phononic&lt;/strong&gt;, an 8-participant mini-symposium in the CSIAM Conference, Hefei, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 16-19, 2021 &lt;strong&gt;Eigenvalue problems: numerical methods and pplications&lt;/strong&gt;, an 8-participant mini-symposium in the Annual Conference  on Computational Mathematics 2021, Nanjing, China, co-organizer(Delayed).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sep 24-26, 2021 &lt;strong&gt;Finite Element, Discontinuous Galerkin and galerkin-type Methods&lt;/strong&gt;, a mini-symposium in the Fifth Jing-Jin-Ji Conference on Conputational Mathematics, Zhangjiakou, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 24-27, 2019 &lt;strong&gt;Finite Element, Discontinuous Galerkin and Galerkin-type Methods&lt;/strong&gt;, an 11-participant mini-symposium in the FOurth Jing-Jin-Ji Conference on Computational Mathematics, Tianjin, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 11-16, 2019 &lt;strong&gt;Multigrid methods for multiscale problems&lt;/strong&gt;, a 2-session mini-symposium in International Multigrid Conference (IMG2019), Kunming, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 15-19, 2019 &lt;strong&gt;Finite element exterior calculus and applications&lt;/strong&gt;, a 4-session mini-symposium in 9th ICIAM, Valencia, Spain, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oct 30-31, 2018 &lt;strong&gt;4th PKU Workshop on Numerical Methods for PDEs&lt;/strong&gt;, Peking University, Beijing, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 14-17, 2016 &lt;strong&gt;Efficient computing with finite element methods&lt;/strong&gt;, a 4-session mini-symposium in MAFELAP, London, UK, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aug 10-14, 2015 &lt;strong&gt;Numerical Methods for Multi-physics Problems&lt;/strong&gt;, a 4-session mini-symposium in ICIAM 2015, Beijing, China, co-organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 6-10, 2015 &lt;strong&gt;Development on Non-Self-Similar Domain Decomposition and Multilevel Methods&lt;/strong&gt;, a 3-session mini-symposium in DD23, Jeju, Korea, co-organizer.(Cancelled due to MERS)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Publications</title>
        <link>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/publications/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dong020524.github.io/posts/publications/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;(ORCID ID: 0000-0001-5490-5401) (*:corresponding author)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Representative works]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;An optimal piecewise cubic nonconforming finite element scheme for the planar binarmonic equation on general triangulation&lt;/em&gt;, Science China Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;64&lt;/strong&gt;(2021) 2579-2602.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Minimal consistent finite element space for the biharmonic equation on quadrilateral grids&lt;/em&gt;, IMA Journal of Numerical Analysis, &lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt;(2020), no. 2, 1390-1406.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Regular decomposition and a framework of order reduced methods for fourth-order problems&lt;/em&gt;, Numerische Mathematik, &lt;strong&gt;138&lt;/strong&gt;(2018), 241-271.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mixed schemes for quad-curl equations&lt;/em&gt;, ESAIM: Mathematical Modelling and Numerical Analysis, &lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt;(2018) 147-161.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Stable finite element pair for Stokes problem and discrete Stokes complex on quadrilateral grids&lt;/em&gt;, Numerische Mathematik &lt;strong&gt;133&lt;/strong&gt;(2016), 371-408.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Jinchao Xu: &lt;em&gt;Optimal solvers for fourth-order PDEs discretized on unstructured grids&lt;/em&gt;, SIAM Journal on Numerical Analysis, &lt;strong&gt;52&lt;/strong&gt;(2014), 282-307.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Ming Wang: &lt;em&gt;A nonconforming finite element method for the Cahn-Hilliard equation&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Computational Physics &lt;strong&gt;229&lt;/strong&gt;(2010), 7361-7372.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[highlight papers]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yingxia Xi, Xia Ji, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A multi-level mixed element scheme of the two dimensional Helmholtz transmission eigenvalue problem&lt;/em&gt;, IMA Journal of Numerical Analysis &lt;strong&gt;40&lt;/strong&gt;(2020), 686-707.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner of the First-Class Award of Excellent Youth Paper of Chinese Computational Mathematical Society. August, 2019. (by Y. Xi)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;9&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, Ming Wang: &lt;em&gt;A posterior estimator of nonconforming finite element method for fourth-order elliptic perturbation problems&lt;/em&gt;, Jurnal of Computational Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt;(2008), 554-577.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner of the Second-Class Award of Excellent Youth Paper of Chinese Computational Mathematical Society. November, 2007.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;10&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Huilan Zeng, Chensong Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Optimal quadratic element on rectangular grids for $H^1$ problems&lt;/em&gt;, BIT Numerical Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;61&lt;/strong&gt;(2021) 665-689.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winner of the Second-Class Award of Excellent Youth Paper of Beijing Computational Mathematical Society. August, 2020. (by H. Zeng)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Original peer-review papers]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;11&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huilan Zeng, Chen-Song Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;On the existence of locally-defined projective interpolations&lt;/em&gt;, Applied Mathematics Letters, &lt;strong&gt;accepted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qing Liu, Tiexiang Li, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;A mixed element scheme of Helmholtz transmission eigenvalue problem for anisotropic media&lt;/em&gt;, Inverse Problem &lt;strong&gt;39&lt;/strong&gt;(2023), Paper No. 055005, 17 pp..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wenjia Liu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A lowest-degree strictly conservative finite element scheme for incompressible Stokes problem on general triangulations&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Scientific Computing, &lt;strong&gt;93&lt;/strong&gt;(2022):28.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huilan Zeng, Chen-Song Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;: A low-degree strictly conservative finite element method for incompressible flows on general triangulations&lt;/em&gt;, SMAI Journal of Computational Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt;(2022), 225-248.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qi Jiang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, Lin Wan: &lt;em&gt;Dynamic inference of cell developmental complex energy landscape from time series single-cell transcriptomic data&lt;/em&gt;, PLOS Computational Biolugy, &lt;strong&gt;18.1&lt;/strong&gt;(2022): e1009821.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qimeng Quan, Xia Ji, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A lowest-degree quasi-conforming finite element de Rham complex on general quadrilateral grids by piecewise polynomials&lt;/em&gt;, Calcolo, &lt;strong&gt;59&lt;/strong&gt;(2022):5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yingxia Xi, Xia Ji, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Order reduced schemes for fourth order eigenvalue problems on multiply-connected polygonal domains&lt;/em&gt;, Numerical Mathematics: Theory, Methods and Applications, &lt;strong&gt;14&lt;/strong&gt;(2021), No. 4, pp. 920-944.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yingxia Xi, Xia Ji, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;A simple low-degree optimal finite element scheme for the elastic transmission eigenvalue problem&lt;/em&gt;. Communications in Computational Physics, &lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt;(2021), pp. 1061-1082.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, *Stable mixed element schemes for plate models on multiply-connected domains, Advances in Applied Mathematics and Mechanics, &lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt;(2020), No. 4, pp. 1008-1034.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yingxia Xi, Xia Ji, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;A high accuracy nonconforming finite element scheme for Helmholtz transmission eigenvalue problem&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Scientific Computing &lt;strong&gt;(2020) 83:67&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew Gilette, Kaibo Hu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Nonstandard finite element de Rham complexes on cubical meshes&lt;/em&gt;, BIT Numerical Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;60&lt;/strong&gt;(2020) 373-409.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weifeng Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Order Reduced Method for Quad-curl Equation with Navier Type Boundary Condition&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of COmputational Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;38&lt;/strong&gt;(2020) No.4, 565-579.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ronghong Fan, Yanru Liu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Mixed element methods for quad div equations&lt;/em&gt;, Computational Methods in Applied Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;19&lt;/strong&gt;(2019), N0. 2, 341-357.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wei Gong, Zhiyu Tan, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A robust block diagonal preconditioner for elliptic optimal control problems with mixed finite element method&lt;/em&gt;, Numerical Linear Algebra and Application, &lt;strong&gt;25&lt;/strong&gt;(2018), e2129.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fei Wang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Optimal Quadratic Nitsche Extend Finite Element Method for Interface Problem of DIffusion Equation&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Computational Mathematics, Vol. &lt;strong&gt;36&lt;/strong&gt;(2018), 693-717.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, Yingxia Xi, Xia Ji: *A multi-level mixed element method for the eigenvalue problem of biharmonic equation, Journal of Scientific Computing, &lt;strong&gt;75&lt;/strong&gt;(2018), 1415-1444.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuyan Chen, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A conservative stable finite element method for Stokes flow and nearly incompressible linear elasticity on rectangular grid&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Computational and Applied Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;323&lt;/strong&gt;(2017), 53-70.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zheng Li, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;A stable mixed element method for biharmonic equation with first-order function spaces&lt;/em&gt;, Computational Methods in Applied Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;17&lt;/strong&gt;(2017), no. 4, 601-616.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shangyou Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;$C_0P_2-P_0$ Stokes finite element pair on sub-hexhadron tetrahedral grids&lt;/em&gt;, Calcolo, &lt;strong&gt;54&lt;/strong&gt;(2017), no. 4, 1403-1417.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jun Hu, Xueqin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Capacity of the Adini element for biharmonic equations&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Scientific Computing, &lt;strong&gt;69&lt;/strong&gt;(2016), 1366-1383.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chunsheng Feng, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;Optimal solver for Morley element problem for biharmonic equation on shape-regular grids&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Computational Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt;(2016), 159-173.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xiangyun Meng, Xueqin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: *Convergence analysis of the rectangular Morely element scheme for second-order problem in arbitary dimensions, Science China Mathematics, &lt;strong&gt;59&lt;/strong&gt;(2016), 2245-2264.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruth Jinru Cheng, Xuehai Huang, Shi Shu, Jinchao Xu, Chensong Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*, Zhiyang Zhou: &lt;em&gt;Application of an energy minimizing algebraic multigrid method for subsurface water simulation&lt;/em&gt;, Int. J. Numer. Anal. Model. &lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt;(2013), 374-388.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ming Wang, Penghe Zu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;*: &lt;em&gt;High Accurancy Nonconforming FInite Element Methods for fourth-order Problems&lt;/em&gt;, Science China Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;55&lt;/strong&gt;(2012), 2183-2192.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jinchao Xu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Norms of discrete trace functions of $H^1(\Omega)$   and $H^2(\Omega)$&lt;/em&gt;, COmputational Methods in Applied Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;12&lt;/strong&gt;(2012), 4, 500-512.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boran Gao, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;, Ming Wang: &lt;em&gt;A note on the nonconforming ffinite elements for elliptic problems&lt;/em&gt;, Journal of Computational Mathematics &lt;strong&gt;29&lt;/strong&gt;(2011), 215-226.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Original peer-review book chapters]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;37&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jinchao Xu, &lt;strong&gt;Z.&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Optimal finite element methods for interface problems&lt;/em&gt;, in Proceeding of the 22nd International Conference of Domain Deconposition, 77-91, Springer International Publishing,2016.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
